Hanasakajin-san!
White to Grandpa and Grandma, too!
I just laughed.
Seino! Galgal Channel GO!
Read aloud without laughing! Today, I would like to do something called "read aloud without laughing".
There is a story in here, and we are going to read it aloud.
Each time you read the story, you will be asked to do something like this.
Each time we read, there is a theme to set up. If you laugh or something, you will eat this chalk.
If you laugh or something, you eat this chalk. When you think you have laughed, you eat it.
When it runs out, the person who has the most chalk loses. If you finish the reading with this chalk still in your hand, we will decide the best read-aloud award by voting.
It's a game of "replace. Let's all take it seriously.
To be honest, I don't think I'll make it big. It depends on the subject.
Shall we continue? Chapter 1.
Don't laugh. I'll read from there.
I think I'm going to laugh.
What?
Like that blue character. National love.
National
This is the first time I've ever heard of this possibility.
I'm working on it.
hmm
Practice of this
Nobita
I wonder if it's just lines
Hanasaka Shrine
Okay, everyone!
One step at a time.
Shut up!
Let's hear it louder.
What should I do?
This is bad.
Tell me it's bad.
I've never done anything like this before.
Chapter One
Here, there, doggy doggy doggy.Koko hare wan wan
Once upon a time
Once upon a time there was an honest and good-natured old man and woman
They played at being cute and idol-like
Let's do it that way.
They had no children of their own
So they loved the cute little girl as if she were their own child.
They loved him like a real child.
Don't laugh!
It's like kabuki.
But it's easy to do.
Do this, everyone!
Shiro was very attached to his grandparents.
They loved him.
That's good!
That's great!
Like stairs.
I like it that way.
In the house next door
There was a greedy old man and a greedy old woman.
Oh, that's good.
It was very atmospheric.
with something on the belt.
and saying, "What is this?
while saying, "What is it?
the old man put a hoe in it.
and there's a click.
and there's something shiny and glittering.
like a child just learning to speak
It's so hard
As he dug deeper and deeper
I found a lot of shiny koban
That's good!
That's good.
Like a playTheater style.
Why do you always do this kind of thing?
The old man was so surprised
He called his grandmother in a loud voice
and brought the koban into the house
Like in Takarazuka
It's like that character now.
Look at this
See? See? And...
What? But...
Do it right.
Pun.
Poof! Poof!
Pun pun!
The way the character enters
If it doesn't go in, it's not right.
Something's wrong with me.
Zusan, are you in this time?
Stop it!
It's only good when you're reading, right?
You said I shouldn't laugh.
Until you put in the characters...
The good-natured old man and grandmother...
They became rich.
Oh!
I have to admit, it was still good.
End of Chapter One
Finally, chapter one.
Five.
Three.
Two.
You sound like you've got two.
I'm not good at it.
Chapter 2
Pines of the Broad PinePine of the Broad Pine Tree
I made a mistake.
The neighbor who heard the rumor
The greedy old man next door
He was so envious
He was always starting to buy
He came to borrow White.
I was always picking on him.
What did you say?
He was starting to buy them.
And White's pine tree pine tree
That one.
That's a little...
That's right.
It's more than I'm saying.
Like a newscaster.
It's better to be slow.
Honest old man is a good man.
I lent him White.
And became a crybaby.
Long
The greedy old man
Isn't there koba buried in my field too?
Where is it, where is it, where is it
he said
I put it on White's neck
"Where is it?
Why aren't you laughing?
That's great.
Are the readers laughing?
I thought you were laughing.
It's funny.
It's like TV shopping.
I love it.
Yeah, it's good.
It's a terrible drag.It's a terrible pull.
White was
In pain.
Turn over.
I've caught him.
Hooked.
It's a TV shopping video.
That's the image I had in mind.
That was terrible.
I know what you mean.
That's White's border.
That's what White looks like.
I have four.
Three.
Six.
Announcer.
Lose.
Let's boo boo! Let's say the same line over and over again.
Arellies, let's dabble in the arellies, those who are confident, let's say it, let's say it, let's say it, let's say it
I'll cut you off, I'll cut you off, I'll cut you off, I'll cut you off, I'll cut you off, I'll cut you off, I'll cut you off, I'll cut you off
I've already bought these beauties...
What? Why isn't it showing up?
There's a place called Onigashima, far out at sea, where bad demons live in a castle.
There's a place called Onigashima in the distant sea... and there's a castle full of bad demons... from the land of the wayward.
They're protecting the treasure they've been working so hard to get.
Well, there's a place called Onigashima at the end of the distant sea.
There's a place called Onigashima, far out at sea, where bad ogres live in a castle and protect the treasure they stole from the Land of Ways and Means.
Well, at first the expression on his face was a bit vague, but that's about it...
There's a place called Onigashima at the end of the sea...
I think I may have already touched it
There's a place called Onigashima, where bad ogres live in the back, guarding the treasures they've stolen from the land.
They protect the high treasures they've stolen from the people of the land.
It's true... the southern version... it's a little bit difficult...
It's a little difficult... there's a place called Onigashima...
There's a place called Onigashima, where wicked demons live in the back, guarding the treasures they've stolen from many lands.
They say they're guarding it and they're guarding it, but it's a matter of how you say it.I'm protecting you and you're protecting me, but both say they're protecting me, it's just a matter of how you say it.
I like it. In the castle.
It's like rap.
Pentaracocco, right? But wait, wait, wait. Look at number 8. Pentaracocco.
Let's do this one. Let's do this one together, like a rap song.
Pentarakocco, pentarakocco, pentarakocco, pentarakocco, pentarakocco, pentarakocco...
Pentaracocco, Pentaracocco, Petaracocco, Pentaracocco.
I like that he doesn't read it.
I don't think the person on the other side of the screen is laughing at all.
I don't know if you think this video is good or not, but even if you don't think it's good, please subscribe to my channel.
I don't know if you think this video is good, but even if you don't think it's good, please subscribe to my channel and leave a comment!
I'm wearing Folik's outfit this time!